Hello Hello Friends Welcome to another episode
of our blogs Meet and Hospital So Guys
today's video is going to cover a topic that is
very important, we do not subscribe to the vehicle,
so this is
talking about insurance, you need to subscribe
before taking it, so today we will talk
about this thing, please subscribe before starting the video
and if you liked the video then do
like and share it, I
was a subscriber to my channel, so approximately 800 to 1000 people
visit our channel, they love us,
watch us, they like it, but if you have
not subscribed to the channel then please
press that red button, subscribe to the channel
and also press the bell icon, so let's
start the video, ah
how could you sleep Mahendra, this
is the ball, so Guys, what I am going to talk about in the video today,
this specific life is
not only for Royal Enfield, friends,
seriously, Royal Enfield is
not the only brand, but you can use it for anyone, so first of all let
me tell you
that there is insurance, now the insurance for new
vehicles is for five years  There are two types of insurance which are
taken which is one year comprehensive
insurance and four years
compliant. The subscribed parties have a total of
five years insurance and those whose
vehicles are more than one year old
or those whose vehicles are insured
before the implementation of this note, then they
have two types of options and one in
which there is subscription and the
second type of insurance is
only third party so let me tell you in a
little detail about all these insurances
and what benefits you get in these
and what benefits
you do not get at all so whenever you go for
insurance, the
first thing you should check in your vehicle
insurance is
what is the ID value of your vehicle IDBI value
means identified value, that is the
valuation of your vehicle is being put by the
insurance company because the
subscription is based on that only, so first point you
must subscribe for Rs.220000
and if you want then in this the loss of
time can be
spread by half. If your vehicle is stolen or gets completely destroyed then
you have
Rs.26010 but the insurance company  The
amount that you will get from this will be only of Rs.150000
because the ID of your vehicle
is also Rs.150000, so first of all, you
must check the ID of your vehicle and the
depreciation of ID that happens every year, that is, the
decrease that happens, is 10 percent standard, that is,
last year the value of your vehicle was
Rs.180000, so this year after 10 percent, the
value of your vehicle will be Rs.180000 -
Rs.18,000, that is Rs.106000, that is
one point, the second point that
you have to see is that
before renewing your insurance policy, you must
see that your third party insurance is
limited or a limited
liability, if it is limited liability, then
on any type of claim, if you have to pay to the third party, then the
insurance company will not bear more than Rs.6000,
and its subscribe video is being appointed with someone else,
maximum amount of your
development of India, in that you can pay Rs.6000.
You will have to pay the full liability subscription but if instead of that
you have a limited liability policy, it
is unlimited or a normal policy, then in that
you will get a third party claim of approximately one lakh rupees,
so
you must subscribe to this thing, the
second point is that every year
if you do not take it on the insurance policy, then
you get a no claim bonus in it, in
response to the first subscription you will renew the insurance from the second year
and if you have not taken any claim then
you get a no claim bonus of 20%, on
top of this the salary increases in the third year, then
25% in the fourth year, after that 50% in
this way it keeps increasing, this is done, the
second thing is subscription is important, if you are
buying a new car soon then you should
subscribe and doing what you do, you
must get it in your policy as soon as possible, now in
case of the accident, if
your car is totaled 40, then
you will get the invoice value of your car i.e.
ex-showroom, you will also get the
amount you have paid for registration
and
along with that whatever you have paid to the insurance company  If
you get this, then this policy is called
RTI Return to Involve. It is approximately 5
% more expensive than the normal policy. Along with
this, another cover that you
need to look for in it is the Desperation Reaction policy. There are
two types of policies of Desperation
Without Condom and Reaction with Consumables. That is,
if you have a Depression policy
and your car meets with an accident, then you will
not have to bear any cost of parts,
you will only have to pay for mobiles and
file charges. Now
what is included in these consumables? These include
your nuts, bolts, any type of
lubricant, any type of substitution.
If you have a normal one, then you will have to pay for these things.
Parts from the file, which is
war, but if you have a substitution,
you do not have to pay a single penny. The car
substitution is available only to the subscriber.
Now, along with this, there are
some other covers in insurance policies which we probably
never ask for, or we can say that the
first point that the dealership or our insurance agent tells us about is the enjoyment cover
policy.  In which if you
go to any previous video, that is, water damage
occurs because
you do not get any insurance cover for this by default,
but if you have taken cover, then the
second thing you will get is if you renew the insurance policy for
electrical and
electronic bulbs, that is,
here I am saying that
like if you have installed a laggard in your vehicle
and if you have defined the value of that laggard at the
time of taking or buying your policy, there is an
option of Additional
Services, if you go into it and define that value
of your laggard, then in case of any accident,
if you have installed any additional lights,
but if you have got them
covered by electrical ex-serviceman in the insurance, then you
get a claim for your lights also, but its
process is that you should have the original bills of that light
and after removing the
depreciation of the person you have defined for the light,
you get the remaining cost, that is,
one more thing which you can
see in your policy is roadside
assistant money, so most of the companies,
if I tell my customers, especially Royal
Talking about Enfield, they provide free insurance for a year
and if you want, you
can also purchase additional insurance from them. But there are many
companies which, to
give a lucrative benefit to their customers,
also provide roadside assistance coverage during the one-year policy. So
you can also get RSS, but
for this you will have to check. The fourth and very
important thing which is very
important for you to check is that you enter the
expiry date of your policy, your engine
number, your chassis number and your policy number.
If you are booking a policy, then
enter the details of all these things very appropriately and correctly. If you make
any mistake while entering it, then you may face
problems at the time of claim. The
last point which I
would like to tell all our subscribers here is that
if you take an insurance policy on gas
and whenever you make a claim, then
along with the claim, an SMS will
definitely come from the company on your mobile.  In which the
name of your claim saver and his contact number is
also given, which if you subscribe quickly, then
you will get that claim number there
and you can
call the claim and know the status of your attitude, which
parts you have received approval for and
which you have not received. So and
finally, I would like to tell you one more thing
that please look at our job skin without insurance. The
last point I would definitely
like to say is that please subscribe, please do not
drive your car on the road. The reason behind this is
only to save the papers from the police.
If you are going on the road and you have an
accident with your car and if
you have insurance and a valid driving
license, then you
can avoid a huge legal sale because if you have a
Valentine's Day certificate
and along with it you have valid insurance, then
your
insurance company will support you in settling any legal problem with the vehicle that has collided with your car. If you
have any legal case against you, then the
insurance company will have to support you there also.
But if you are going on the road, it is an
empty road, there is no one there,
I will go even without insurance, there is no
problem, if any
accident happens and that party makes a
claim on you, then you can get into a lot of trouble, I
hope you liked
our video today,
especially about all the details of insurance,
so guys please use your insurance
wise list, with this, I am requesting you guys for the last time,
please if you liked the video, then please
like and share it and do
not forget to subscribe to the channel, I will meet you
very soon, festival from mother subscribe
[music]
to
ki a kar do kar
do